<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>SciPy Conferences - The SciPy2014 organizers</title><link href="https://conference.scipy.org/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://conference.scipy.org/feeds/the-scipy2014-organizers.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://conference.scipy.org/</id><updated>2014-05-15T00:00:00-05:00</updated><entry><title>Early Bird Extension and new Keynote</title><link href="https://conference.scipy.org/news/2014/05/15/early-bird-extension-and-new-keynote/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2014-05-15T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2014-05-15T00:00:00-05:00</updated><author><name>The SciPy2014 organizers</name></author><id>tag:conference.scipy.org,2014-05-15:/news/2014/05/15/early-bird-extension-and-new-keynote/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Early Bird registration extended to May 22nd and Nick Coghlan will now be Keynoting.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Early Bird registration has been extended&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early Bird registration has been extended until May 22, or the first 300 registrants, so be sure to &lt;a href="https://conference.scipy.org/scipy_registration/registration.php"&gt;register today&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A preliminary schedule, subject to change, has been posted on &lt;a href="https://conference.scipy.org/scipy2014/schedule/"&gt;the website&lt;/a&gt; .  There are two days of tutorials, three days of talks, and then two days of sprints -- wow!  There's certainly something to please everyone, including talks on technology, visualization, and domain science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;New Keynote Speaker!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're pleased to announce Nick Coghlan as a keynote speaker for the SciPy conference.  Nick is a CPython core developer, a Fellow of the Python Software Foundation. He is the author or co-author of several accepted Python Enhancement Proposals, including PEP 343 (which added the with statement and context managers to the language), and PEP 453 (which integrated the "pip" package manager with the CPython installation process). Nick has also accepted a number of PEPs on Guido van Rossum's behalf, and is the current default BDFL-Delegate for packaging related PEPs.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="SciPy"></category></entry><entry><title>Why I SciPy</title><link href="https://conference.scipy.org/news/2014/04/22/why-i-scipy/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2014-04-22T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2014-04-22T00:00:00-05:00</updated><author><name>The SciPy2014 organizers &lt;scipy-organizers@scipy.org&gt;</name></author><id>tag:conference.scipy.org,2014-04-22:/news/2014/04/22/why-i-scipy/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Looking for stories around why you participate in the SciPy community.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Why I SciPy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SciPy is many things to many people.  It can be an opportunity to learn about the newest technologies or maybe old ones that you should have been using.  It is a chance to learn about new and exciting features of the packages you use the most.  SciPy is also a chance to reconnect to old friends and meet new ones. For many, it is also an opportunity to develop your skills as a scientific software developer and become a better scientist overall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what makes you SciPy?  We are looking for a short paragraph explaining the reasons why you SciPy. Including specific instances or reasons why the conference has had a positive impact on your science are the best!  For example,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I SciPy because it is a place where I can learn about new python packages I can leverage in my science and old packages I should have been using.  I go to learn about new and exciting features of the packages I use the most.  It is also about developing my own skills as a scientific software developer, learning about best practices and new ways to make my own work more effective.  I of course go to see old friends and make new ones.  Most of all, I SciPy to become a better scientist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please send submissions to
scipy-organizers@scipy.org or post to Twitter or G+ using the hashtag #whyiscipy. We'll post the best submissions of the week to future mailings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to hearing your story!&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="SciPy"></category></entry><entry><title>SciPy2014 Registration Open</title><link href="https://conference.scipy.org/news/2014/04/12/scipy2014-registration-open/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2014-04-12T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2014-04-12T00:00:00-05:00</updated><author><name>The SciPy2014 organizers &lt;scipy-organizers@scipy.org&gt;</name></author><id>tag:conference.scipy.org,2014-04-12:/news/2014/04/12/scipy2014-registration-open/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Time to register for SciPy2014&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Registration is Now Open!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Registration for SciPy 2014 is now open!  The number of submissions this year has skyrocketed, and we're excited about an amazing program.  Early bird registration will last until May 6, or 300 registrants - whichever comes first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Register today! (https://conference.scipy.org/scipy_registration/registration.php)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to two and a half days of talks, there will as always be two days of tutorials, two days sprints, and a half-day workshop on Thursday afternoon on sustainable scientific software (WSSSPE (http://wssspe.researchcomputing.org.uk/) ).  See you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Excellent Submission Turnout&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year we had a total of 133 talk and poster submission to SciPy. With three days of talks and approximately 24 talks per day, there are about 72 slots, for a full and exciting week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also received 32 tutorial submission for 16 slots over 2 days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally the SciPy John Hunter Excellence in Plotting Contests received 18 submissions this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Meet Us At PyCon 2014&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are PyCon 2014 and would like to talk about ScIPy 2014 feel free to stop by the Enthought booth in the Expo Hall, or tweet @SciPyConf or @scopatz!&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="SciPy"></category></entry><entry><title>SciPy2014 Submissions, Diversity Funding</title><link href="https://conference.scipy.org/news/2014/04/12/scipy2014-submissions-diversity-funding/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2014-04-12T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2014-04-12T00:00:00-05:00</updated><author><name>The SciPy2014 organizers &lt;scipy-organizers@scipy.org&gt;</name></author><id>tag:conference.scipy.org,2014-04-12:/news/2014/04/12/scipy2014-submissions-diversity-funding/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Submissions due soon, Diversity Funding opportunity&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;April 1 - Final Submission Deadline!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The final deadline for submitting talks, tutorials, posters, and application for sponsorship deadline is April 1, 2014!  This is the last warning that the submissions will be closed so please mark your calendars now. As always, please take a look at a few talks (http://conference.scipy.org/past.html) from previous years, our guidelines for this year (https://conference.scipy.org/scipy2014/participate/presentations/) , and we look forward to reviewing your submissions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submit your abstracts today (https://conference.scipy.org/scipy2014/) !&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We particularly encourage introductory-level tutorial submissions. This is a great opportunity to help inform a new group of Python users on the basics they need to start solving problems with SciPy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;SciPy 2014 Diversity Funding Announcement&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The thirteenth annual Scientific Python conference, SciPy 2014, will be held in July in Austin, TX. The SciPy community knows that the more people who are involved in scientific problem-solving, the better off we all will be because the diversity of perspectives leads to a diversity of solutions. Therefore, in an effort to increase the diversity, as well as the pool of people who are able to attend the conference, there are now an additional 5 funding opportunities available, thanks to generous support from NumFOCUS. To apply for this funding, supply the information indicated on the financial aid application site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also encourage those interested in Diversity in Scientific Computing (DISC) to consider registering for the DISC luncheon. Registration for the lunch will be available during registration for the conference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The SciPy 2014 Diversity Committee
* Patricia Francis-Lyon
* Katy Huff
* Leah Silen
* Kristen Thyng&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="SciPy"></category></entry><entry><title>Deadline Extension</title><link href="https://conference.scipy.org/news/2014/03/15/deadline-extension/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2014-03-15T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2014-03-15T00:00:00-05:00</updated><author><name>The SciPy2014 organizers &lt;scipy-organizers@scipy.org&gt;</name></author><id>tag:conference.scipy.org,2014-03-15:/news/2014/03/15/deadline-extension/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Submission deadline extended until April 1!&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Submission deadline extended!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to popular demand, the deadline for submitting talks, tutorials and posters has been extended to April 1, 2014 - no 'foolin!'  We encourage submissions related to general scientific computing with Python, one of the two special themes for this year, or the domain-specific mini-symposia held during the conference.  Take a look at a few talks (http://conference.scipy.org/past.html) from previous years, our guidelines for this year (https://conference.scipy.org/scipy2014/participate/presentations/) , and we look forward to reviewing submissions!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submit your abstracts today (https://conference.scipy.org/scipy2014/) !&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="SciPy"></category></entry><entry><title>Submit, Tutorials, and BOFs!</title><link href="https://conference.scipy.org/news/2014/03/07/submit-tutorials-and-bofs/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2014-03-07T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2014-03-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated><author><name>The SciPy2014 organizers &lt;scipy-organizers@scipy.org&gt;</name></author><id>tag:conference.scipy.org,2014-03-07:/news/2014/03/07/submit-tutorials-and-bofs/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Submission announcement, Community efforts, Tutorial details, and GSOC&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Submissions close in a week!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next Friday, March 14th, the submissions for talks, posters and tutorials are due.  We encourage submissions related to general scientific computing with Python, one of the two special themes for this year, or the domain-specific mini-symposia held during the conference.  Take a look at a few talks (http://conference.scipy.org/past.html) from previous years, our guidelines for this year (https://conference.scipy.org/scipy2014/participate/presentations/) , and we look forward to reviewing submissions!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submit your abstracts today (https://conference.scipy.org/scipy2014/) !&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Flock Together&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an effort to increase the opportunities for community building, SciPy would like to emphasize the use of birds of a feather (BoFs) sessions. These sessions usually include short presentations by a panel and a moderator with the bulk of the time spent opening up the discussion to everyone in attendance. We will organize a number of BoFs that are of general interest such as state-of-the-project and BoFs based on the themes of the conference and the mini-symposia topics.  For more information, see our BoF page (https://conference.scipy.org/scipy2014/participate/bofs/) .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some example past BoFs include Reproducibility, Teaching Scientific Computing with Python, The Future of Array Oriented Programming, PyNE Updates, Python and Finance, NumFOCUS, Python in Astronomy, SciPy Next Year, Collaborating and Contributing in Open Science, and the Matplotlib Enhancement Proposal Discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We would like to solicit the community for ideas and organizers for other BoF topics. Please include a small description of the BoF, possible panelists, and whether you would be willing to moderate.  Submissions can be made at the main abstract submission page (https://conference.scipy.org/scipy2014/) .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Present a Tutorial&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SciPy always kicks off with two days of tutorials. These sessions provide extremely affordable access to expert training, and consistently receive fantastic feedback from participants. This year we are expanding the tutorial session to include three parallel tracks: introductory, intermediate, and advanced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The introductory track specifically targets programmers with no prior knowledge of scientific python and to ensure a consistent overall experience, the topics for these sessions have been fixed.  We have a full set of information and guidelines for submission (https://conference.scipy.org/scipy2014/participate/tutorials/) .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are now accepting tutorial proposals from individuals or teams that would like to teach a tutorial at SciPy 2014 -- submissions are due on March 14, and we'd love to see what you have in store.  Whether you are a major contributor to a scientific Python library or an expert-level user, this is a great opportunity to share your knowledge and offset some of the costs of your SciPy 2014 attendance.  Submit your tutorial proposals today (https://conference.scipy.org/scipy2014/) !&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;GSoC @ SciPy 2014&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are pleased to announce celebration of the 10th anniversary of the Google Summer of Code!  We'll be announcing more details soon as well as highlighting specific projects and people involved in 2014.  Stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="SciPy"></category></entry><entry><title>JHEPC and WSSSPE at SciPy2014</title><link href="https://conference.scipy.org/news/2014/03/02/jhepc-and-wssspe-at-scipy2014/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2014-03-02T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2014-03-02T00:00:00-06:00</updated><author><name>The SciPy2014 organizers &lt;scipy-organizers@scipy.org&gt;</name></author><id>tag:conference.scipy.org,2014-03-02:/news/2014/03/02/jhepc-and-wssspe-at-scipy2014/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Announcing John Hunter Excellence in Plotting Contest and Working towards Sustainable Software for Science: Practice and Experience at SciPy 2014&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;John Hunter Excellence in Plotting Contest&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In memory of John Hunter, we are pleased to announce the Second Annual SciPy John Hunter Excellence in Plotting Competition. This open competition aims to highlight the importance of quality plotting to scientific progress and showcase the capabilities of the current generation of plotting software. Participants are invited to submit scientific plots to be judged by a panel. The winning entries will be announced and displayed at the conference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Hunter’s family is graciously sponsoring cash prizes for the contest winners in the following amounts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1st prize: $1000&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2nd prize: $750&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3rd prize: $500&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Instructions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Entries must be submitted by March 21, 2014 via e-mail to plotting-contest@scipy.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plots may be produced with any combination of Python-based tools. (It is not required that they use matplotlib, for example.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Source code for the plot must be provided, in the form of Python code and/or IPython notebook, along with a rendering of the plot in PDF format. If the original data can not be shared for reasons of size or licensing, "fake" data may be substituted, along with an image of the plot using real data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each entry must include a 300-500 word abstract describing the plot and its scientific importance for a general scientific audience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Entries will be judged on their clarity, innovation and aesthetics, but most importantly for their effectiveness in illuminating real scientific work. Entrants are encouraged to submit plots that were used during the course of research, rather than merely being hypothetical.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scipy reserves the right to display any and all entries, whether prize-winning or not, at the conference, use in any materials or on its website, with attribution to the original author(s).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Important dates:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;March 21, 2014: Plotting submissions due&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Winners will be announced during the Scipy conference days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to exciting submissions that push the boundaries of plotting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The SciPy Plotting Contest Organizing Committee:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michael Droettboom, Space Telescope Science Institute (chair)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eric Firing, University of Hawai`i at Manoa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jake Vanderplas, University of Washington&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;WSSSPE Announcement&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are proud to announce that this year on Thursday afternoon of the conference, we will be hosting a Workshop on Sustainable Software for Science: Practices and Experiences (WSSSPE@SciPy).  This will be an opportunity to gather together people from across the SciPy community to collect and understand best practices in sustaining communities of scientific software.  Look for more information on the SciPy conference website, but keep your Thursday afternoon free!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For information about past workshops and the collection of papers selected for the first WSSSPE workshop at Supercomputing 2013, see &lt;a href="http://wssspe.researchcomputing.org.uk"&gt;http://wssspe.researchcomputing.org.uk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Ready, Set, Submit!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a slightly bumpy start abstract submission is now open!  The deadline for abstract submissions is March 14th, 2014. Submissions are welcome that address general scientific computing with Python, or one of the two special themes for this year's conference, or the domain-specific mini-symposia held during the conference. Examples talks from &lt;a href="http://conference.scipy.org/past.html"&gt;previous years&lt;/a&gt; are available online.  We look forward to reviewing you submissions!&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="SciPy"></category></entry><entry><title>SciPy2014 Announcement</title><link href="https://conference.scipy.org/news/2014/02/20/scipy2014-announcement/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2014-02-20T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2014-02-20T00:00:00-06:00</updated><author><name>The SciPy2014 organizers &lt;scipy-organizers@scipy.org&gt;</name></author><id>tag:conference.scipy.org,2014-02-20:/news/2014/02/20/scipy2014-announcement/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;SciPy2014 Announcement&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello All!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are pleased to announce that SciPy 2014, the thirteenth annual Scientific Computing with Python conference, will be held this July 6th-12th in Austin, Texas. SciPy is a community dedicated to the advancement of scientific computing through open source Python software for mathematics, science, and engineering. The annual SciPy Conference allows participants from all types of organizations to showcase their latest projects, learn from skilled users and developers, and collaborate on code development.
For more information please visit our website: https://conference.scipy.org/scipy2014/
This year the conference has been extended to include an additional day of presentations. During the presentation days SciPy is proud to host the following event and talk types:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keynotes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert Panels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short Talks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Poster Presentations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Birds of a Feather Sessions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The full program will consist of two days of tutorials by followed by three days of presentations, and concludes with two days of developer sprints on projects of interest to attendees. This year, we are excited to present a job fair for the first time!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Specialized Tracks&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year we are happy to announce two specialized tracks that run in parallel to the general conference:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scientific Computing in Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to efforts such as Software Carpentry, the Hacker Within and grassroots Python Bootcamps, teaching scientific computing as a discipline is becoming more widely accepted and recognized as a crucial task in developing scientific literacy. This special track will focus on efforts to promote and develop scientific computing education, as well as related topics such as reproducibility and best practices for scientific computing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Geospatial Data in Science&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Python has become a core component of organiziing, understanding, and visualizing geospatial data. This track will focus on libraries, tools and techniques for processing Geospatial data of all types and for all purposes -- from low-volume to high-volume, local and global.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Domain-specific Mini-symposia&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Introduced in 2012, mini-symposia are held to discuss scientific computing applied to a specific scientific domain/industry during a half afternoon after the general conference. Their goal is to promote industry specific libraries and tools, and gather people with similar interests for discussions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mini-symposia on the following topics will take place this year:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Astronomy and astrophysics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bioinformatics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Geophysics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vision, Visualization, and Imaging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computational Social Science and Digital Humanities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engineering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Tutorials&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Multiple interactive half-day tutorials will be taught by community experts. The tutorials provide conceptual and practical coverage of tools that have broad interest at both an introductory or advanced level. This year, a third track will be added, which target specifically programmers with no prior knowledge of scientific python.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Developer Sprints&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A hackathon environment is setup for attendees to work on the core SciPy packages or their own personal projects. The conference is an opportunity for developers that are usually physically separated to come together and engage in highly productive sessions. It is also an occasion for new community members to introduce themselves and receive tips from community experts. This year, some of the sprints will be scheduled and announced ahead of the conference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Birds-of-a-Feather (BOF) Sessions&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Birds-of-a-Feather sessions are self-organized discussions that run parallel to the main conference. The BOFs sessions cover primary, tangential, or unrelated topics in an interactive, discussion setting. This year, some of the BOF sessions will be scheduled and announced ahead of the conference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Important Dates&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Important dates for the conference:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;March 14th : Presentation abstracts, poster, tutorial submission deadline. Application for sponsorship deadline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;April 17th : Speakers selected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;April 22nd : Sponsorship acceptance deadline&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May 1st    : Speaker schedule announced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May 6th or 150 registrants: Early-bird registration ends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;July 6-12th: 2 days of tutorials, 3 days of conference, 2 days of sprints&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to a very exciting conference and hope to see you all in Austin this summer!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The SciPy2014 Organizers&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="SciPy"></category></entry></feed>